tweetboard.com 2010-05-13

# Tweetboard - True Twitter Conversation

## Privacy Policy 

140Ware (”Tweetboard“) takes the private nature of your personal information very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use any website available from 140Ware. Please read this notice very carefully. It is 140Ware policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, 140Ware collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. 140Ware purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how 140Ware visitors use its website. From time to time, 140Ware may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

140Ware also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. 140Ware does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. Please be aware that 140Ware cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of other sites, including those to which we link or whose products or services we reference. We encourage you to read the terms of use and privacy statements of each Web site you visit.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to 140Ware websites choose to interact with 140Ware in ways that require 140Ware to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that 140Ware gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at 140Ware to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with 140Ware are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, 140Ware collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with 140Ware. 140Ware does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

140Ware may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, 140Ware may monitor the most popular links on the site. 140Ware may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, 140Ware does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

140Ware discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on 140Ware‘ behalf or to provide services available at 140Ware websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using 140Ware websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. 140Ware will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, 140Ware discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when 140Ware believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of 140Ware, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a 140Ware website and have supplied your email address, 140Ware may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with 140Ware and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. 140Ware takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. However, if 140Ware or any of its products is sold to a new owner, whether by merger, stock sale, asset sale or other means, we retain the right to transfer your profile, Site Data and all other content, data and information to this new owner, provided the owner agrees to respect the Privacy Policy in effect with respect to this personal data.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. 140Ware uses cookies to help 140Ware identify and track visitors, their usage of 140Ware websites, and their website access preferences. 140Ware visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using 140Ware‘ websites, with the drawback that certain features of 140Ware websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, 140Ware may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in 140Ware sole discretion. 140Ware encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

*This Privacy Policy has been adapted from a policy originally published by Automattic (makers or WordPress) and is made available under the Creative Commons Sharealike license.[](http://bit.ly/1JtNr)
